[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie Eminem plays the main character, whose name is Jimmy B-Rabbit Smith, Jr.", "correct_answer": "8 Mile", "incorrect_answers": ["Torrance Rises", "The Wash", "The Slim Shady Show"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the Maitake mushroom mean?", "correct_answer": "Dancing mushroom", "incorrect_answers": ["Born from the rain", "Mother of earth", "Lover of he dawn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What American Idol finalist was born on March 25, 1984, in Los Angeles, California?", "correct_answer": "Katharine McPhee", "incorrect_answers": ["Elliott Yamin", "Jennifer Hudson", "Kelly Clarkson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Mias cats name in the film The Princess Diaries?", "correct_answer": "Fat Louie", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlotte", "Joey", "Helen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country gave the Statue of Liberty to the United States as a centennial gift?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Canada", "England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the odd one.", "correct_answer": "Vixen", "incorrect_answers": ["Viper", "Adder", "Cobra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The piece known as the rukh is found in this variation of chess.", "correct_answer": "shatranj", "incorrect_answers": ["shatar", "shogi", "makruk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In historical atlases published in Germany, Germany is traditionally painted in light blue. What color is traditionally used for England?", "correct_answer": "Pink", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Purple", "Yellow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the chemical symbol of Einsteinium, a rare earth metal named after Albert Einstein.", "correct_answer": "Es", "incorrect_answers": ["Et", "Ei", "E"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Michael Corleone give the kiss of death in one of the most memorable scenes of the movie Godfather II?", "correct_answer": "Fredo Corleone", "incorrect_answers": ["Kay Corleone", "Sonny Corleone", "Tom Hagen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food is Pate de coing, which is traditionally served at Christmas in the French region of Provence?", "correct_answer": "Quince jelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Goose pate", "Goat milk cheese", "Mashed potatoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term, denoting an internal organ, also refers to a color which is a mixture of dark brown and grey?", "correct_answer": "Liver", "incorrect_answers": ["Lung", "Kidney", "Spleen"]}]